<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<folder>

    <location
        mapUrl="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Bayanaul+140000,+Kazakhstan/@50.7931301,75.6976247,15z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x4259201f0a2063e7:0x903a36d62022c207!8m2!3d50.7925659!4d75.702517"
        images="images/locations/bayanaul/"
        photo-credit="Name Surname (2022)"
        icon="home"
        x="4100"
        y="1450">
        <text language="en" name="Bayanaul Village">This is Bayanaul Village with population of about 9000 wonderful people.</text>
        <text language="kz" name="(Kz) Bayanaul">(in Kazakh) This is Bayanaul Village with population of about 9000 wonderful people.</text>
        <text language="ru" name="(Ru) Bayanaul">(in Russian) This is Bayanaul Village with population of about 9000 wonderful people.</text>
    </location>

    <location
        mapUrl="https://goo.gl/maps/XzgQvYNc8BEGMRBW9"
        images="images/locations/zhasybai/"
        photo-credit="Name Surname (2022)"
        icon="swim"
        x="3550"
        y="1550">
        <text language="en" name="Lake Zhasybai"> Zhasybai is the most beautiful lake of Bayanaul National Park. The place is unique in its history and nature. For example, this reservoir is considered the cleanest in Kazakhstan. 
• The infrastructure is not sufficiently developed, so resting in some recreation areas. The time machine will take you back to the Soviet period. Romantic, isn't it? Many holiday homes are clean and cozy, but the living conditions are often Spartan. However, do not be afraid because nature and sincere people compensate for some inconveniences. Rixos Hotel is being built on the shore of Lake Zhasybai for those who like to relax with the best service and for lovers of wild recreation, campfire food and guitar songs, there is a campsite where you can come with your tent or rent it. 
• From water activities, you will be offered boating, catamarans and inflatable slides. I hope you enjoy it on Zhasybai!</text>
        <text language="kz" name="(Kz) Lake Zhasybai">(in Kazakh) Zhasybai is the most beautiful lake of Bayanaul National Park.</text>
        <text language="ru" name="(Ru) Lake Zhasybai">(in Russian) Zhasybai is the most beautiful lake of Bayanaul National Park.</text>
    </location>

    <location
        mapUrl="https://goo.gl/maps/YCLuAXqfm8LkAzrVA"
        images="images/locations/toraigyr/"
        photo-credit="Name Surname (2022)"
        icon="swim"
        x="4700"
        y="1651">
        <text language="en" name="Lake Toraigyr">At Lake Toraigyr rises the Peak of the Brave. the rock bears this name recently - from the 1950s, when the mass development of tourism in the Bayanaul mountains began.</text>
        <text language="kz" name="(Kz) Lake Toraigyr">(in Kazakh) At Lake Toraigyr rises the Peak of the Brave. the rock bears this name recently - from the 1950s, when the mass development of tourism in the Bayanaul mountains began.</text>
        <text language="ru" name="(Ru) Lake Toraigyr">(in Russian) At Lake Toraigyr rises the Peak of the Brave. the rock bears this name recently - from the 1950s, when the mass development of tourism in the Bayanaul mountains began.</text>
    </location>

    <location
        mapUrl="https://goo.gl/maps/NNovPBRxqFo6vTWy9"
        images="images/locations/kempirtas/"
        photo-credit="Name Surname (2022)"
        icon="mount"
        x="4650"
        y="1900">
        <text language="en" name="Kempirtas Rock">Another miracle of nature is the rock Kempirtas or Baba Yaga.  On the one hand you will see an old woman, and on the other the appearance of a young girl.</text>
        <text language="kz" name="(Kz) Kempirtas Rock">(Kz) Another miracle of nature is the rock Kempirtas or Baba Yaga.  On the one hand you will see an old woman, and on the other the appearance of a young girl.</text>
        <text language="ru" name="(Ru) Kempirtas Rock">(Ru) Another miracle of nature is the rock Kempirtas or Baba Yaga.  On the one hand you will see an old woman, and on the other the appearance of a young girl.</text>
    </location>

    <location
        mapUrl="https://goo.gl/maps/7mg5QVLQPopXpuei7"
        images="images/locations/akbet/"
        photo-credit="Name Surname (2022)"
        icon="mount"
        x="3850"
        y="2050">
        <text language="en" name="Akbet">Akbet is the highest mountain peak in Pavlodar region.</text>
        <text language="kz" name="(Kz) Akbet">(Kz) Akbet is the highest mountain peak in Pavlodar region.</text>
        <text language="ru" name="(Ru) Akbet">(Ru) Akbet is the highest mountain peak in Pavlodar region.</text>
    </location>

</folder>
